Next customer.
Um, can I get a kid's meal?
Huh?
What was that, sir?
Can I get a kid's meal?
Speak up. There's
a lot going on here, honey.
Can I get a kid's meal?
I don't see no kids.
Yeah, I don't have
a kid with me.
I'm gonna eat it.
Well, only a kid can order
a kid's meal.
That's not true.
I know that's not true.
Oh, yeah, it is.
Only a kid can order it.
So a kid has to wait in line
and order a kid's meal.
A kid can't get
an adult meal?
Look here, sir,
you have to be
14 or younger
to get a kid's meal.
I've just been made
day manager,
and I didn't get that title
by handing out discounted meals.
Look, you don't have to be a kid
to get a kid's meal, okay?
Do you have to be a Evander
Holyfield to get the champ?
Okay, do you have to be
fucking Chubby Checker
to get the Chubby Decker?
Do you need to have
a long foot to--
that one doesn't translate,
but you know--
This is ridiculous, okay?
Can I just please get
a kid's meal?
Can I get a cup for water?
Sure.
Here you are.
-Thank you.
-Have a good day.
Next.
(Kodak Black's "Skrt"
playing)
*
* Girl, I'm done with you
* Girl, we done,
it's through *
* I hit that
for the work *
* Stick and move,
then I skrt, skrt, skrt *
* Skrt, skrt
We need to get
a new revenue system.
I'm getting paid
direct deposit tomorrow,
but it's not gonna be a lot.
I barely signed anyone up
at the airport.
You only get paid
a commission, though, right?
(scoffs)
You might as well sell drugs.
Yeah.
How do you make money?
I sell drugs.
It's lucrative.
Yeah, man, it's easy.
People are addicted to them.
Mm-hmm.
Sell it till you get rich.
How else you pay
for studio time,
clothes, videos, and weed
without a lame-ass job?
Yeah, but, you know,
you're more famous now.
Your profile's risen,
which means more risk, you know?
You can't go to jail, man.
We'll be careful
out there, man.
Out where?
Highway.
Got to see the Mexicans.
Going to see the Migos.
You know I'm going strapped.
(blows)
(muted TV sounds in background)
Yeah, well just--
just try not to die.
Every day.
Yeah, just so y'all know,
there's probably a bullet
in here somewhere.
Noted.
(hip-hop plays in background]
(door opening)
-Hey, what's up?
All right, honey,
time to go to bed.
Hi.
No, don't get up.
I wouldn't want you
to have to pick up Lottie
and ruin all that
you're doing.
I just got here.
I thought you were gonna
pick her up today, right?
Honey,
is it really that hard
to help me out
every once in a while?
I even have to take her
to your parents' place myself.
Really, Earn?
Is this about having to
bail me out?
Please, you really think
you're the first boy
I've bailed out of jail?
Yeah.
EARN: I was working
at Al's all day.
Yeah? You smell like work.
What is that?
-Kush?
-Super Jack.
Nigga, don't.
Don't what?
Be happy?
I never ride you for you doing
what you want to do
with your life.
No, you roll your eyes at me
and you call me crazy
any time I try
to tell you something.
I guess that's just me, right?
I'm crazy-ass Vanessa.
(exhales sharply)
Whatever.
I've been inconsiderate.
I get it.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I want to take you to dinner.
-No, it's too late.
-It's too late?
Yeah, you messed up.
Can I buy you dinner
and watch you eat it
from across the room?
You know, I can get
one of those corny niggas
to eat it with you.
I know you love them.
"Oh, I love your energy.
My dreads are in a bun.
"Hey, have you heard
any music from the '90s?
-It's all amazing."
-You know what?
You're lucky that I like
corny-ass dudes.
Mm-hmm.
Talking about you.
Why are you always turning me
into the angry black woman?
-'Cause you are.
-Are you kidding me?
-I'm the stereotype?
-Mm-hmm.
While your ass,
you can't even take care
of your own goddamn kid?
I'm fine with being
a stereotype.
-It's working out great for me.
-Really?
Yeah, obviously I'm in a bed
and I'm technically homeless.
It's pretty great.
(laughing)
I don't know about all that.
It was a hard day.
(sniffing)
-You like it.
-I love it.
(chuckles)
(groans)
Come on, dog.
How are you broke on payday?
What are you,
"12 Years a Slave"?
Yeah, my name is
"12 Years a Slave."
-The slave.
-Shut up, nigga.
You don't know his name.
I gotta take Van out
on this date.
And then the math of the money
I need for the week,
including this MARTA card,
I only have $62 left over.
Yo, yo, yo, $62 is plenty enough
to go on a date, man.
Well, you--hey, you know what?
Take her out
to the Indigo Lounge.
What's that?
It's a little spot
in mid-town I go to.
Taking a couple of my hos.
(chuckles)
You know, the ones I really
like, like Eve and Jessica.
Yeah, dog.
It is nice in there.
And, you know the best part
about it?
They got the happy hour menu
popping all night after 7:00.
-Word?
-Yeah.
It's nice in there, man.
You'll like it, dog.
Drinks be like five bucks.
Should go check it out, bro.
A'ight. Bet.
I'll talk to you later.
Yes, sir.
Hand dog out.
Yo, I know you was not just
listening to my conversation.
Girl, you are some mess.
Shit,
I might just win tonight.
MAN: Hey, man.
It's gonna be quick, a'ight?
Don't let Earn spook you
and shit.
-Spook me?
-Mm-hmm.
Man, I ain't scared of nothing.
I got Daddy right here.
(hip-hop playing)
-You call your gun "Daddy"?
-Yes.
That's weird, man.
Is it weird when your girl
call you "Daddy"?
Man, that's completely
different, and yes, yes.
It is.
All right,
what about Papi?
I know you ain't got no problem
with Papi.
Man, Papi, that's like...
Cultural.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Because it's Spanish,
now all the sudden, it's sexy.
Look,
that shit always creepy.
Man, if a bitch called me
"Daddy,"
man,
something wrong happened.
Real talk.
Yo, you not gonna see this,
but your assumed perversion
of the word "Daddy,"
I think that's stemming from
the fear of mortality, man.
-What you call your gun?
-Nigga, gun.
(phone vibrates)
Hold on.
Ah, it's on.
9:00 tonight.
(trills, laughs)
Let's do it.
I'm gonna handcuff
the briefcase to my wrist.
Why?
'Cause it's professional,
nigga.
We ain't no duffel bag boys.
Okay.
(mellow hip-hop music)
*
I don't...
see any parking here.
I don't know.
This is kind of a weird street.
No, no, it's good.
I think
we should just valet.
No, no, I'll find
street parking, okay?
Patience.
Patience, young Vanessa.
(mellow hip-hop plays]
Ah, see?
Perfect.
-Wait, here?
-Yeah.
-No, I don't think so.
-Come on, it'll be fun.
-Oh. Oh, no.
-There we go.
I don't know.
Why don't you go ahead and park
it right here, young blood?
Don't be scared, darling.
Just smellin' hard work on me.
-That's all.
-Oh, I know. I know.
No, you're fine till midnight.
Uh, you guys close
at midnight?
Uh, no, no, sir.
Street gang.
They--they like out come out
at around 11:00,
vandalize the cars
and joyride 'em.
Not a large cop presence
around here, huh?
Well, no,
but the towing companies.
But don't worry
about getting towed,
'cause like I said,
I'm out here.
You see these five cars, right?
These my people.
And if you eat over there
at that restaurant over there,
I'll come over there
and let you know
if you gotta move it
real quick.
Okay, I'm sorry, but, like,
what kind of a parking lot
is this?
Because it seems
janky as hell.
No, no,
it ain't no parking lot.
No, I found
this vest over there
at the Kroger shopping center.
And this here
is a lightsaber.
Luke Skywalker.
-How much--how much is it?
-Uh, $10.
That's how much
the valet costs.
-Well, $8.
-Oh, uh-uh.
Earn, you are taking my car
to valet right now.
I'm sorry,
this is ridiculous.
-I'm sorry.
-$6.
-Good night.
-Come on, now.
Hey, we all we got.
Hey, come on.
EARN: $6 isn't bad.
Hey!
(funky pop plays)
I'm gonna hit it, man.
both: * Your
I'm gonna hit that one.
both: * Good love
* Deserves an encore
* Your good love
(music stops)
You know how to get
to Main Street?
Change of plans.
Follow me.
(Shabazz Palaces'
"An Echo From the Hosts
That Profess Infinitum"
playing)
*
* All that diamond dust
* Flowin' up your hose
* Flamboyant obstacles
* Deals made to cope
* Wow
Ignore the truths *
* Shots at all
of these soft, huh? *
* Ideas in recline
* Rise of the lost
* Yea, yea
The hell is this?
These niggas are tripping.
(music plays distantly)
Hey.
Did you get the handcuff key
off the table?
(Max P's "Gang" playing)
Hey, Qua.
They're here.
Hey, yo, bring 'em in.
-What's happening?
-Ah, you know.
Busy, busy.
What the hell you mean,
nigga?
-Trapping bored as fuck.
-(chuckles)
Yeah, but you know
how it is.
-(speaks indistinctly)
-Oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Hey, hold up, hold up.
We gotta handle this first.
Go on.
* And if my cuz slackin' I'll
pay to see my bro get 'em *
-(grunts)
-Sh--
You ain't gotta do this.
Please.
What the fuck?
(man crying)
Get this nigga his clothes.
(sobbing)
Please, man, Q, come on.
Don't do this to me, yo.
Hold up, put your clothes on,
man, it's cold out here.
-(whimpers)
-* If you don't gang bang
* Gang bang,
gang, gang, gang *
* Diamonds on my neck,
my chain swanging *
(mouthing words)
(man mumbling tearfully)
Are you guys ready to order?
Yeah, I haven't been able
to find your happy hour menu.
-Oh, we don't do that anymore.
-What?
Yeah, we got a new owner
from New Orleans.
He's kind of changing it up.
We do mostly seafood now.
Not the tapas and stuff,
but it's really good.
Well, I think I'm gonna start
with a drink.
-Okay.
-Um, I was looking
at the Bayou Breeze,
but what do you think?
Should I get that or the wine?
Definitely the Bayou Breeze.
It's my favorite.
-Okay, okay.
-It's a house special, yeah.
Um, what are
your soups of the day?
We have Aunt Zora's
seafood soup.
It has a lot in it.
Like fish, crab, mussels,
squid.
$28.
Do you have anything else?
No, that's the only soup
we offer.
-No, that sounds really good.
-It's so good.
You're gonna love it.
Well, I was think--
You know, the shrimp puffs
go really great with that soup.
I'm gonna throw in
an order of those, too.
For free?
(laughter)
-You can share them with her.
-Yeah.
It'll be a good idea.
We can share.
We'll share them.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Uh, tap water's fine.
Earn, I can't drink
by myself.
Do you have
a Miller High Life?
-Like the ones in the can?
-(chuckles)
We got a hipster.
(laughter)
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Do you know what you want
for your entree, Miss?
I'm actually not sure.
What do you think
about the catfish filet?
Well, it's okay,
but actually tonight,
we have a special grilled
scallop and lobster meal.
It's incredible.
You guys seem like
you're having a special night.
That meal would be perfect.
-That sounds really good.
-It's market price.
-That means it's fresh.
-It's really fresh.
-Yeah, I'm gonna have that.
-Okay, great.
I will be right back
with those drinks.
-Okay, thank you.
-Thank you.
Who are you texting?
Nothing, no one.
What?
Oh, you're doing that weird
sad boy face you get sometimes.
That's just my face.
I have to look like that.
What, um--how--how's work?
Actually, oh, my God,
it has been crazy.
Did I tell you about
that girl, Janine, last week?
She was sniffing Wite-Out
in my class.
Yeah, I think--I want to hear
about this,
but I have to check
on one thing, one thing.
Hey, could you
ring up my order
and tell me how much
I'm spending?
I just got something
that's market price.
Wow.
Broke as fuck, my nigga.
Yes.
(man sobbing)
Please, y'all.
(whispers)
Did you check your shoes?
Why the fuck would the key
be in my shoes?
Stop being scary, nigga.
Figure it out.
You know what, Marcus?
I'ma let you go.
(whimpering)
You know my son, man.
-Please don't, man.
-Start heading that way, man.
It's all good.
You'll find the city.
(whimpering)
Shit.
Ah, shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
Oh, shit, shit. Oh, shit.
Hand me Percy over there.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. Shit.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
(gunshot)
* Gang, gang, gang, gang
gang *
Hmm.
* Diamonds on my neck,
my chain swanging *
Did you check your jacket?
(exhales)
Yeah, man.
I just think we need
a chance as humans
to...fail
in order to discover
what actually works, you know?
People don't think there's
a process to being happy.
(soft dinner music plays)
So what do you want?
I don't know.
I mean, I guess I just
want a chance to find out.
Who doesn't?
Mm.
I get the whole
"follow your dreams" thing,
but, um, our daughter needs
all the tools to survive,
and...
that includes you, Earn.
*
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Uh-oh.
Does she need a brownie sundae?
We'll just take the check.
How about I go get
the dessert menu,
and I'll come back
and we can--
Just get us the check and stop
trying to upsell me on shit.
You're killing me tonight.
You've been fucking
killing me.
Okay.
(dinner music continues)
*
(breathes)
Fuck...
So, Al, tell me how
you disappeared and then show up
out the blue
with this big-ass order, man.
Man, you know
I'm rapping, man.
It ain't been that long now.
Rapping?
You just got arrested, dog.
No. Uh, I didn't--
(scoffs)
-No, man. Arrested?
-For murder.
You was locked up
for murder, right?
Now you back?
Man, that's kinda fast, dog.
Man, he nervous as hell.
Look at him.
He's shaking.
Well, it's a drug deal,
so it's total vibes.
Yo, yo, are we gonna--we gonna
do business or like...
(phone vibrating)
You gonna answer that?
(continues vibrating)
Put that motherfucker
on speakerphone too, man.
(clears throat)
Hello, cousin.
How are you today?
Listen, man,
can you do me a huge favor
and put $20 in my account,
like,
transfer it over ASAP, like,
you gotta help me out, man.
-All right.
-Really?
(exhales/laughs)
Thanks, man, you--
You're saving my ass.
Okay, man, well, you know
I gotta go now.
Okay, cool.
So, what are you guys doing
right now?
You and Darius do that deal?
Do not know what
you mean.
The ones with the Mexicans,
you guys had the guns.
You guys were, like, "We ain't
scared of you guys," you said.
Yo, okay, man,
all right, nigga.
Sending money.
All right, peace out.
Man...
(stammering)
-Good guy. He's legit.
-With all that, yeah.
He's cool.
Why didn't you tell him--
Stop talking, man.
It's weird that your card
didn't work
the first two times
they swiped it.
Yeah...
[exhales] let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're not tipping her?
Come on, it's not enough
that she makes less than you
because you got a dick?
Have some class.
No, I'm just here to see...
Mr. Fogle, they towing your car.
Come on.
Hey, man, my bad
for all of them guns, man.
You know, we had to make sure
you was straight.
We heard some weird shit
about you, man.
(door opens)
Hey, sorry I'm late.
Paper Boi, right?
I'll fuck with
that postal mixtape. (laughing)
All right, man.
Okay.
-(laughing)
-Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
-Who dat?
-That's my cousin, Tanqueray.
I told you we rap now,
right?
-No, word?
-Yeah, he good,
but he talks a lot,
you know, he crazy.
But anyway,
let's settle this deal.
-Let's get it handled.
-Okay.
Well,
it's in the briefcase.
Uh, but I-I left the key
at home.
So--kinda stuck.
We can solve that.
See,
we'll just take the money,
and y'all get to keep
the briefcase.
-It's easy.
-Cool.
-We see y'all.
-All righty.
Hey, yo,
what'd you call
ya'll group, man?
-We the Migos.
-Yeah.
That Four Migos.
We're inseparable.
(chuckles)
(crickets chirp, owl hoots)
(inhales deeply)
Man, that nigga look like
he gonna die tonight.
There is a security job
at the office building,
so you could save for a car,
and then you wouldn't have to
take our daughter
on the bus with weirdos.
I'm gonna become somebody
I hate at a job like that.
Well,
you're doing that already.
You know, being a rapper
is something
that a high school kid
wants to do.
Unlike opening
a fashion boutique,
which is super unique.
I know I have a daughter.
And I know
she deserves the best.
But I don't think
I have to compromise
what I want out of life
to do that.
Especially if I think
it's gonna provide for her.
You know me, Van.
I can do this.
I just gotta do it my way.
And if you can't do this
out of love for me...
Do this out of love for her.
That's some dumb shit.
That's some dumb-ass shit,
Earn.
(sighs)
I'd like to report
a debit card stolen.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, champagne's the worst.
(Migos "Spray the Champagne"
playing)
* Oh, spray the champagne
spray the champagne *
* Spray the champagne
* Young got the crown
* Young, young
got the crown *
* Young OG's
they respect us *
* OG's
young got the crown *
* Uh, spray the champagne
spray the champagne *
* Spray the champagne
* Spraying champagne
on the sofa *
* End of the couch
with Louboutin loafers *
* 2,500
I put in the sole *
* We got the crown and my,
this is golden *
* Hocus pocus you know
that I be exposured *
* And I be thanking God
everyday *
* 'Cause it's chosen
* So many gold chains
on my neck it turned gold *
* I be whipping and driving the
Lamborghini like it's stolen *
* Salute to the OG's
who gave us the crown *
* Shout-out to the migo
said biting the style *
* When I'm on stage
drippin' like it rain *
* Sprayin' champagne
all over the damn crowd *
* Ain't part of the squad
then don't come around *
* Ain't a young rich